hang on hang
on good day Joe today's date's the 25th
oh not the of of
February
2012 not
1492 okay yeah but it could be if you
like to be all right what do you got Joe
you got some magnets you're just going
to stop them up aren't you these are
nothing on the bench they nothing see
they just Fage not any strength
lift them off with your little finger
see but magnets are meant to be stronger
if you put two together and that's how
they normally come together which is
north and south or south and north
however put two on makes no difference
put 100 on there's no more gas what they
call strength none all right so you put
your washer in everything else and so on
now the washer is non-magnetic you
understood all right so you put them
together what does come on you actually
remove what was
there there's none still with your
little finger was there still take it
off with your little finger easier okay
all right easier there's none there yeah
it's not attracting at all is it that's
gone but what you shouldn't be able to
do which we show you is you don't get
them
together
so you do and
then you hear that mhm why don't you try
two hands underneath there and see if
you can and three
feet come on you're pulling the magnet
away come on lift it up see my
chin the same thing here the other week
and it finally one of the magnets let go
and punch me there and I'll bled
everywhere this is on funnyest Home
Videos to wait there wa you got to get
your chin away yeah and you that's
come on just lift it
Joe I'm trying oh that was a near nose
job I'm trying yeah that's one
pole okay and then all you do is you
turn back and what do you got
nothing the magnetism isn't in the
magnets the magnets are a a solid um
material you got visible and invisible
you understand so the invisible is the
power source and you can't find it
because you can't see it so really in
the magnets and everything else this
pull pull push whatever
else
isn't there what do you
see okay and it's definitely not in
there but I bet it's on the other side
of that magnet Jo sorry it's on the
other side of the magnet it's on the
other side yeah yeah come on sh come on
it's got to be can't can't just a head
it like that well what you need is
another bit of Steel for
that so you think that you're right um
this
way
okay it's on the washer but don't go to
don't go to the
magnets okay but what's on the other
side not a lot of
anything nothing so we go back this way
which is the normal way that they do
come together and what do we
got and what do we got on that
one one go there just one go there so
that means two bits of Steel not two
magnets two bits of Steel won't go
together which
aren't
magnets okay but the other thing is too
if you look this powder you know Iron
fallings and powder and on these
magnets mhm well what you find is when
you do these right you find it on there
see that there it's on there because it
didn't go to
this you ever heard of opposite
Eagle I've heard of it for every action
there's an opposite and equal Y and then
for every opposite equal there's a
opposite equal equal opposite and then
opposite that is another opposite and
then opposite all of opposites is the
opposite opposite which is
equilibrium so the opposite
opposite isn't an
opposite does that make sense does that
mean it's where you started no never
where you
started you don't know where you start
why because everything's in
circles no you're not Jo you're still on
two feet yeah so you want Square it off
and everything Gose we'll give you a
diagram somebody wants to know where to
go what to do and everything else okay
you at the front of the house here right
go to the corner turn
left bottom of Street you're going to
find a
roundabout okay take your left hand turn
then you're going to come down to a y
intersection take the left hand turn
then you come up to a
t-section take the left hand turn then
you come up to another offset T section
take the left hand turn when you get
back to here to be short ass blonded if
follow stand that front telling you
where to
go and in the circle hang on show us the
the short ass bit we still haven't seen
in a
circle uh you can't find the starting
point and you haven't got an ending
point and on the
magnetism doesn't seem to